BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code 6755: UFCW No. 428/Safeway, 2001-2007 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  9/2/01-9/11/04, 9/12/04-12/1/07; 2 of 2
- Code 6758: UFCW No. 400/Safeway, 1992-2008 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  9/12/92-9/21/96, 3/21/96-3/25/00, 3/26/00-3/27/04, 3/28/04-3/29/08
- Code 6759: UFCW No. 789, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  3/5/89-2/29/92; 1 of 2
- Code 6759: UFCW No. 789, 1992-2008 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  3/1/92-3/4/95, 3/5/95-3/1/98, 3/1/98-3/2/02 (with duplicate); 2 of 2
- Code 6760: UFCW No. 328 and 1445/Stop and Shop Supermarket, 1994-2004 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  2/13/94-2/8/97, 1/1/97-2/10/01, 2/11/01-2/14/04
- Code 6761: UFCW No. 371/Stop and Shop, 1976-1988 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  3/7/76-12/9/78, 12/6/81-2/9/85, 3/17/85- 2/6/88; 1 of 2
- Code 6761: UFCW No. 371/Stop and Shop Supermarket, 1991-2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  2/10/91-2/12/94, 2/13/94-2/8/97, 2/9/97-2/10/01; 2 of 2
- Code 6762: UFCW No. 1099/Kroger, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  10/9/94-10/9/99
- Code 6763: UFCW No. 1099/Meijer Stores, 1995-2009 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  3/31/95-4/22/00, 4/26/00-4/3/04, 4/25/04- 4/25/09
- Code 6764: UFCW No. 1099/Meijer Stores, 1996-2005 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  5/2/96-10/7/00, 10/22/00-10/8/05
- Code 6766: UFCW No. 99/Fry's Food and Drug Stores, 1994-2008 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  9/18/94-10/26/97, 10/26/97- 10/29/00, 12/22/97-10/29/00, 10/30/00-10/25/03, 3/19/03-10/25/08, 10/26/03-10/25/08
- Code 6767: UFCW No. 99/Safeway, 1994-2008 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  9/18/94-10/25/97, 10/25/97-10/28/00, 10/29/00- 10/25/03, 3/23/03(10/26/03)-10/25/08
- Code 6771: UFCW No. 56/Acme Markets/Supermarkets General, 1971-2004 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Code 6774: UFCW No. 56/Super Fresh Food Markets, 1994-2008 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  10/30/94-10/31/98, 11/1/98- 11/1/03, 11/2/03-11/1/08
- Code 6775: UFCW No. 1500/Big V. Supermarkets/Shop Rite, 1994-2006 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  9/14/94-9/19/98, 9/20/98- 9/21/02, 3/31/02-9/23/06
- Code 6779: UFCW No. 7/Safeway, 1987-1999 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  5/3/87-5/5/90, 5/6/90-5/8/93, 5/9/93-5/11/96, 6/30/96- 7/10/99
- Code 6780: UFCW No. 455/Kroger, 1993-2004 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  10/23/93-2/28/98, 4/2/95-4/1/00, 3/1/98-4/1/00, 4/2/00-4/3/04
- Code 6783: UFCW No. 1116, 1993-2005 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  12/27/93-4/30/99, 4/30/99-4/29/02, 4/30/02-4/29/05
- Code 6784: UFCW No. 27/Acme Markets, 1997-2003 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  9/28/97-9/23/00, 11/6/03
- Code 6805: UFCW No. 27/Giant Food Inc., 1996-2004 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  7/16/96-3/25/00, 3/26/00(3/21/00)- 3/27/04(3/20/04)
- Code 6814: UFCW No. 1262/Foodtown Supermarkets, 1987-2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  4/5/87-4/7/90, 4/8/90-4/10/93, 5/29/93-4/12/97, 4/13/97-4/14/01
- Code 6819: UFCW No. 227/Kroger, 1987-1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  9/27/87-10/6/90, 10/7/90-10/8/94, 10/9/94- 4/11/99
- Code 6820: UFCW No. 951/Meijer Inc., 1999-2007 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  4/25/99-4/26/03, 9/14/03-9/8/07
- Code 6821: UFCW No. 876/Kroger, 1987-2004 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  8/9/87-1/4/92, 1/5/92-1/4/97, 1/5/97-3/4/01, 3/5/01- 6/5/04
- Code 6822: UFCW No. 876/The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1992-2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  1/5/92-1/4/97, 1/8/95-1/10/98, 1/11/98-3/4/01, 3/5/01-6/5/04, 1/1/01-6/1/07
- Code 6830: UFCW No. 1262/Pathmark Stores, 1997-2001 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  4/13/97-4/14/01
- Code 6836: Retail, Wholesale, and Chain Store Employees Union No. 338, 1995-2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  10/1/95- 10/3/98 and 10/4/98-10/5/02
- Code 6839: UFCW No. 81/Allied Employers Inc., 1986-2004 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  5/4/86-5/7/89, 5/7/89-5/3/92, 5/3/92- 4/30/95, 4/30/95-5/3/98, 5/3/98-5/6/01, 5/6/01-5/2/04
- Code 6843: UFCW No. 2008/Kroger, 1994-2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  6/19/94-6/27/98, 6/28/98-6/29/02, 6/30/02- 6/24/06
- Code 6844: UFCW No. 1262/Edwards Super Food Stores, 1997-2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Code 6855: UFCW No. 23/Penn Traffic, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Code 6857: UFCW No. 428/Albertson's Inc., 2001-2004 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  9/2/01-9/11/04
- Code 6858: UFCW No. 174/General Industry and Pork Stores/Greater New York Meat Trade Institute, 1992-2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  6/20/92-6/3/95, 6/3/95-4/16/99, 4/17/99-6/20/03, 5/8/99-5/9/03
- Code 6860: UFCW No. 881 and 1540/Dominick's Finer Foods, 1993-2003 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  9/26/93-7/27/96, 7/26/96- 11/6/99, 11/7/99-11/9/02, 11/10/02-7/26/03
- Code 6861: UFCW No. 371/Waldbaum's Foodmart, 2001-2009 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  7/1/01-10/2/04 and 10/1/04- 2/28/09
- Code 6864: UFCW No. 711, 1997-2008 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  9/8/97-9/9/01, 2/6/01-9/12/04-2/29/08
- Code 6869: UFCW No. 1657/Bruno's Inc., 1988-2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  9/25/88-9/28/91, 10/1/95-9/25/99, 9/26/99- 9/27/03
- Code 6870: UFCW No. 1657/Bruno's Inc., 1990-2003 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  10/4/90-2/26/94, 2/27/94-2/28/98, 9/26/99- 9/27/03
- Code 6871: UFCW No. 1557 and 1995/Kroger, 1981-2004 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  5/10/81-5/19/84, 5/29/94-11/1/97, 11/2/97-5/11/02, 1/31/00-5/15/04
- Code 6872: UFCW No. 7/King Soopers, 1993-2004 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  5/9/93(5/23/93)-5/11/96(5/26/96), 6/30/96- 7/10/99, 7/11/99-9/11/04
- Code 6875: UFCW No. 7/Safeway, 1983-2004 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  9/11/83-9/13/84, 7/27/84, 9/17/89- 9/19/92, 1992-1996, 3/21/96-3/25/00, 3/21/00-3/19/04
- Code 6872: UFCW No. 400/Giant, 1986-2008 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  9/14/86-9/16/89, 9/17/89-9/12/92, 9/13/92-9/21/96, 3/21/96-3/25/00, 3/26/00-3/27/04, 3/28/04-3/29/08
- Code 6878: UFCW No. 88/Dierbergs National Schunks, 1993-2007 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  6/6/93-6/5/99, 6/6/93-9/23/00, 9/24/00-9/28/03, 9/29/03-9/30/07
- Code 6882: UFCW No. 1262/Shop Rite Supermarkets, 1990-2001 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  4/8/90-4/10/93, 5/29/93-4/12/97, 4/13/97-4/14/01
- Code 6883: UFCW No. 7/King Soopers, 1993-1999 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  5-8/93-5-8/96 and 6/30/96-7/10/99
- Code 6886: UFCW No. 7/Safeway Stores, 1993-1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  5/9/93-5/11/96 and 6/30/96-7/10/99
- Code 6888: UFCW No. 400/Kroger, 1992-2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  7/16/92-3/30/96, 3/31/96-3/24/01, 3/25/01- 3/26/05
- Code 6892: UFCW No. 400/Tyson Foods, 1993-2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  2/15/93-5/4/96, 11/1/98-11/1/01, 10/28/01- 10/30/04
- Code 6893: UFCW No. 400/Shoppers Food Warehouse, 1993-2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  4/21/93-2/4/97, 9/4/96-7/1/00, 7/2/00-3/27/04
- Code 6894: UFCW No. 1059/Meijer Inc., 1993-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  5/6/93-3/16/97 and 8/8/96-5/12/01
- Code 6895: UFCW No. 1500/Pathmark Stores/King Kullen Grocery, 1991-2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  6/16/91-6/18/94, 6/19/94-6/20/98, 6/21/98-6/22/02, 6/23/02-6/24/06
- Code 6896: UFCW No. 342-50/Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1992-1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  11/1/92-10/29/95 and 10/29/95-10/30/99
- Code 6897: UFCW No. 880/Akron-Canton Food Industry, 1996-2005 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  9/8/96-9/12/99, 9/12/99-9/8/02, 9/9/02-9/11/05
- Code 6898: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees Union No. 342-50, 1992-1999 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  10/18/92-10/21/95 and 10/21/95-10/23/99
- Code 6899: UFCW No. 328 and 1445/Stop and Shop Supermarket, 1994-2007 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  Meat Division. 2/13/94-2/8/97, 1/1/97-2/10/01, 2/11/01-2/14/04, 2/15/04-2/17/07
- Code 6902: I.A.M.A.W/Greater St. Louis Automotive, 1976-2004 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  District 9.
- Code 6917: Teamsters No. 974/Minneapolis Automobile Dealer's Association, 1963-2006 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Code 6920: I.A.M.A.W. No. 701/Standard Automotive, 1973-2001 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Code 6921: Teamsters No. 731 Garage Attendants Agreement, 1988-2002 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  8/1/88-7/31/92, 8/1/92- 7/31/95, 8/1/95-7/31/98, 8/1/98-7/31/02
- Code 6925: UFCW No. 1996 and 442/Kroger, 1987-2001 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  11/29/87-11/2/91, 6/28/91-11/8/97, 11/9/97-11/10/01
- Code 6928: UFCW No. 919/Stop and Shop, 1994-2004 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  2/13/94-2/8/97, 2/9/97-2/10/01, 2/11/01- 2/14/04
- Code 6929: UFCW No. 1459/Stop and Shop, 1994-2004 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Code 7117: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union No. 11/Hotel-Restaurant Employers' Council, 1992-2004 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  4/16/92-4/15/98 and 4/16/98-4/15/04
- Code 7302: UFCW No. 1001/Fred Meyer, 1995-2005 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  2/1/95-1/31/98, 2/1/98-1/31/01, 2/1/01- 1/31/04
- Code 7306: UFCW No. 555/Fred Meyer, 1993-2005 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  4/4/93-6/8/96, 11/13/94-7/19/97, 6/14/99-6/15/02, 6/16/02-6/18/05
- Code 7308: UFCW No. 881/American Drug Stores, Inc., 1994-2001 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  10/25/94-8/9/97 and 8/10/97- 8/12/01
- Code 7310: UFCW No. 1099/CVS, 1997-2008 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  10/12/97-10/14/00, 10/15/00-10/11/03, 10/12/03- 10/11/08
- Code 7400: UFCW/American National Insurance Company of Galveston, Texas, 1996-2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  5/1/96- 4/30/98, 5/5/98-5/4/01, 9/1/01-5/4/04
- Code 7403: Office and Professional Employees International Union No. 35/Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1988- 2005 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Code 7406: SEIU No. 25 Agreements, 1975-2006 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Code 7409: SEIU No. 32B-32J/Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, 1985-2006 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Code 7410: SEIU No. 32B-32J/Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, 1966-1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Code 7410: SEIU No. 32B-32J/Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, 1993-2004 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Code 7411: SEIU No. 32E/Bronx Realty Advisory Board, 1967-2005 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Code 7412: SEIU No. 32E/Building and Realty Institute of Westchester and the Mid-Hudson Region, 1997-2003 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  10/1/97-9/30/00, 10/1/00-9/30/03
- Code 7413: SEIU No. 1 Janitors Agreement, 2000-2003 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  4/10/00-4/6/03
- Code 7417: Office and Professional Employees International Union No. 153/New York Stock Exchange/SIAC, 1994-2001 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  2/28/94-11/1/97, 2/4/98-11/3/01
- Code 7419: Office and Professional Employees International Union No. 32/Blue Cross and Blue Shield of New Jersey, 1994-2000 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  5/1/94-4/30/97 and 5/1/97-4/30/00
- Code 7420: SEIU No. 6/American Building Maintenance, 1997-2003 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  10/1/97-7/1/00 and 7/1/00- 6/30/03
- Code 7421: International Union of Operating Engineers No. 94-94A-94B/Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, 1995-2003 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  1/1/95-12/31/97, 1/1/01-12/31/03
- Code 7423: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 986/GTE North Incorporated, 1999-2002 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  10/31/99-10/26/02
- Code 7424: UNITE of the Philadelphia and South Jersey District Council/Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association, 1997-2003 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  6/1/97-5/31/00 and 6/1/00-5/31/03
- Code 7425: U.A.W./Blue Cross and Blue Shield of Michigan, 1996-2002 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  9/1/96-8/31/99 and 9/1/99- 8/31/02
- Code 7426: SEIU No. 87/San Francisco Maintenance Contractors Association, 1985-1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  7/15/85- 2/28/88, 10/3/89-7/31/93, 8/1/93-7/31/96, and 8/1/96-7/31/99
- Code 7427: UFCW No. 1444/Wisconsin Physicians Service Insurance Corporation, 1991-2008 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  11/9/91- 11/11/94, 11/12/94-11/14/97, 11/15/97-11/10/00, 11/11/00-10/8/04, and 10/9/04-10/10/08
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry No. 855/Public Service Electric and Gas Company, 1992-2002 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  5/1/92-4/30/96 and 5/1/96-4/30/02
- Code 7445: Office and Professional Employees International Union No. 39/CUNA Mutual Insurance Society, 1997-2001 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  4/1/97-3/31/01; 1 of 2
- Code 7445: Office and Professional Employees International Union No. 39/CUNA Mutual Insurance Society, 2001-2004 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  4/1/01-3/31/04; 2 of 2
- Code 7510: Hotel and Restaurant Employees No. 25/Hotel Association of Washington DC, 1984-2007 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  9/16/84-9/15/86, 9/16/86-9/15/89, 9/16/95-9/15/98, 9/16/98-9/15/01, 9/16/01-9/15/04, 1/15/05-9/15/07
- Code 7511: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union No. 2/The Hotels, 1985-1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  8/14/89-8/14/94 and 8/14/94-8/14/99
- Code 7517: H.E.R.E. No. 681/Walt Disney World Co., 1997-2004 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  2/1/97-1/31/00 and 2/1/00- 1/31/04
- Code 7526: H.E.R.E. No. 54/Casino Hotels of Atlantic City (Bally's), 1989-1999 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  9/15/89-9/14/94 and 9/15/94-9/14/99
- Code 7532: SEIU No. 752 and 535/Yosemite Concession Services Corporation, 1992-2002 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  3/15/92- 3/14/95, 3/15/95-3/14/98, and 3/15/99-3/14/02
- Code 7540: Culinary Workers Union No. 226/Bartenders Union No. 165/Horseshoe Operating Company, 1994-2002 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  6/1/94-5/31/97 and 6/1/97-5/31/02
- Code 7545: Culinary Workers Union No. 226/Bartenders Union No. 165/Mandalay Resort Group (Circus Circus), 1994-2002 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Code 7550: Culinary Workers Union No. 226/Bartenders Union No. 165/GNLV Corporation, 1994-2007 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  6/1/94-5/31/97, 6/1/97-5/31/02, 6/1/02-5/31/07
- Code 7575: Culinary Workers Union No. 226/Bartenders Union No. 165/Mirage Las Vegas, 1994-2002 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Code 7578: Detroit Casino Council/Motorcity Casino, 2000-2007 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  10/17/00-10/16/03 and 10/17/03- 10/16/07
- Code 7706: UNITE/National Linen Service, 1999-2002 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  5/12/99-5/4/02
- 7712, 1981-2006 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  5/1981 - 6/2006
- 7730, 1992-2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  12/1992 - 11/2003
- 7730, 1995-2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  11/1995 - 11/2003
- 7880, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  6/1998 - 5/2007
- 7881, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- 7882, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- 7883, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- 7884, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- 7885, 1998-2007 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- 7886, 1997-2008 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  4/1997 - 6/2008
- 7887, 1998-2008 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  5/1998 - 6/30/2008
- 7901, 1996-2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  3/1996 - 2/2005
- 7904, 1992-2005 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  11/1992 - 11/2005
- 7906, 1996-2006 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  12/1996 - 12/2006
- 7912, 1998-2004 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  6/1998 - 6/2004
- 7913, 2001-2004 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  6/2001 - 6/2004
- 7915, 2000-2006 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  8/1/2000 - 9/30/2006
- 7919, 1995-2004 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  12/1995 - 10/2004
- 7921, 1996-2005 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  2/1996 - 2/2005
- 7924, 1992-2008 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  6/1992 - 6/2008
- 7929, 1989-2005 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  10/1989 - 9/2005
- 7930, 1998-2005 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  12/1998 - 10/2001 (MOA) - Local 144 Only; 7/1998 - 10/2001 (MOA) - Local 1199 Only; 11/2001 - 4/2005 (MOA) and Booklet - Both locals merged
- 7936, 2005-2008 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  12/2005 - 11/2008
- 7937, 2005-2008 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- 7939, 1997-2008 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  10/1997 - 9/2002; 10/2002 - 4/200; 6/2004 - 4/2008
- 7940, 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  1/8/2001 - 2/5/2005
- 7941, 1997-2007 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  1/1997 - 12/2000; 1/2001 - 12/2004; 4/2005 - 12/2007
- 7943, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  5/15/2005
- 7944, 1992-2009 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  2/1992; 3/1999; 3/2005; 3/2009
- 7946, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  5/2002; 9/2006
- 7950, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  5/2001; 5/2004
- 7951, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  3/2002 - 5/2005
- 7958, 1997-2006 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  4/1997 - 3/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2003; 10/2003 - 10/2006
- 7960, 1999-2005 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 7961, 1999-2005 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  6/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 7962, 1991-2006 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  1991 - 1993; 1994 - 1996; 1998 - 2002; 9/2002 - 8/2006
- 7963, 1998-2004 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  5/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 7964, 2000-2006 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  10/2000 - 10/2003; 10/2003 - 10/2006
- 7965, 1999-2008 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 7966, 1999-2008 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  6/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 7967, 2000-2006 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  5/2000 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2006
- 7968, 1994-2008 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  5/1994 - 4/1997; 10/1997 - 7/2000; 7/2003 - 6/2008
- 7969, 2002-2008 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  7/1/2002 - 6/30/2003; 7/1/2005 - 6/30/2008
- 7971, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  5/2002 - 5/2005
- 7973, 1994-2004 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  10/1994 - 10/1997; 2/2000 - 1/2004
- 7975, 1998-2007 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  10/1998; 4/2001; 4/2001 - 5/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 7976, 1992-2008 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  12/1992 - 11/1994; 12/1994 - 11/1996; 12/1996 - 11/1998; 12/1998 - 11/2000; 12/2000 - 11/2002; 12/2002 - 11/2005; 12/2005 - 11/2008
- 7977, 1992-2008 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  12/1992 - 11/1994; 12/1994 - 11/1996; 11/1998 - 11/2000; 12/2000 - 11/2002; 12/2002 - 11/2005; 12/2005 - 11/2008
- 7978, 1975-2002 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  8/1975; 8/1978; 8/1981; 8/1984; 8/1987; 8/1993; 9/1996 - 8/1999; 9/1999 - 8/2002
- 7979, 2001-2008 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  1/2001 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2008
- 7980, 1975-2003 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  10/1975; 10/1978; 10/1981; 10/1984; 10/1987; 10/1990; 10/1993; 11/1996; 11/1996 - 10/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2003
- 7981, 1996-2006 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  3/1996 - 2/1999; 3/1999 - 2/2003; 3/2003 - 2/2006
- 7982, 1993-2005 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  2/1993 - 1/1996; 2/1996 - 2/1999; 2/1999 - 1/2002; 2/1/2002 - 1/2005
- 7983, 1995-2008 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  4/1995 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2008
- 7984, 1993-2006 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  1/1993 - 12/1995; 1/1996 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2001; 10/2002 - 12/2006
- 7991, 2000-2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  3/2000; 3/2005
- 7992, 1998-2005 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2005
- 7993, 1995-2002 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  9/1995 - 9/1998; 9/1998 - 3/2002
- 7994, 1990-2006 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  10/1990 - 10/1993; 11/1993 - 10/1996; 3/1997 - 2/2000 (and MOA); 2/2000 - 2/2003 (and MOA); 2/2003 - 2/2006 (MOA)
- 7995, 1996-2007 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 3/2002; 4/1/2002 - 3/31/2004; 4/1/2004 - 3/31/2007
- 7998, 1981-2007 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  7/1981; 7/1984; 7/1987; 7/1990; 3/1996 - 3/2000; 3/2000 - 3/2004; 2/2004 - 2/2007
- 8002, 1993-2005 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  11/1993 - 10/1996; 11/1996 - 10/2000; 11/2000 - 10/2005
- 8003, 1989-2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  6/1989; 6/1995; 6/2001; 6/2006
- 8004, 1988-2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  6/1988; 10/1994; 10/1996 - 10/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2004; 3/2005 - 10/2008
- 8005, 1996-2005 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  1/1996; 1/1999; 1/2002; 1/15/2005
- 8006, 1989-2004 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2004
- 8007, 1994-2006 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  9/1994 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2003; 9/2003 - 8/2006
- 8008, 1991-2004 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  1/1991 - 12/1992; 1/1996 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2001; 1/2002 - 12/2004
- 8009, 1991-2007 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  9/1991 - 9/1994; 9/1994 - 9/1997; 9/1997 - 9/2000; 9/2000 - 9/2003; 4/2004 - 4/2007
- 8011, 1986-2006 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  6/1986 - 5/1989; 6/1989 - 5/1991; 6/1991 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8012, 1990-2005 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  2/1990 - 2/1993; 2/1993 - 2/1996; 2/1996 - 2/1999; 2/1999 - 2/2002; 2/2002 - 2/2005
- 8013, 1994-2007 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  2/1994; 2/1996; 2/1998; 6/1998 - 3/2000; 7/2000 - 3/2002; 4/2004 - 3/2007
- 8015, 1994-2006 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  12/1994; 12/1997; 12/1997 - 12/2000; 4/2001 - 12/2003; 4/2004 - 12/2006
- 8017, 1991-2004 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  4/1991 - 12/1993; 1/1994 - 12/1995; 1/1996 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2001; 1/2002 - 12/2004
- 8018, 1992-2007 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  3/1992 - 3/1995; 3/1995 - 3/1998; 3/1998 - 3/2001; 3/2001 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 4/2007
- 8019, 1993-2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  9/1993; 9/1993; 9/1998; 10/1998 - 9/2000; 10/2000 - 9/2002; 10/2002 - 9/2004; 10/2004 - 9/2006
- 8020, 1995-2005 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  11/1995; 11/1998; 11/2001 - 4/2005
- 8021, 1995-2009 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  12/1995; 3/1999; 1/2002 - 1/2005; 8/2005 - 3/2009
- 8022, 1993-2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  12/1993; 1/1/1997 - 10/31/2000; 9/2002 - 12/2006
- 8023, 1992-2009 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  2/1992 - 1/1996; 1/1996 - 1/2002; 1/2002 - 1/2009
- 8024, 1992-2009 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  1/1992 - 1/1996; 1/1996 - 1/2002; 1/2002 - 1/2009
- 8025, 1996-2003 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  5/1996; 5/2000; 6/2000 - 4/2003
- 8026, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  5/2004 - 12/2006
- 8027, 1997-2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 10/2000 - 4/2006
- 8028, 1993-2000 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  6/1993; 6/2000
- 8030, 1992-2007 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  8/1992; 8/1995; 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/2001; 9/2001 - 8/2004; 9/2004 - 8/2007
- 8031, 1998-2008 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  10/1998 - 10/2001; 11/2001 - 4/2005 (MOA); 6/2004 - 4/2008
- 8033, 1991-2006 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  8/1991; 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2003; 7/2003 - 8/2006
- 8034, 1991-2008 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  1/1991 - 1/1993; 1/1993 - 1/1996; 1/1996 - 1/1999; 1/1999 - 1/2002; 1/2002 - 1/2005; 1/2005 - 1/2008
- 8035, 1998-2006 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8036, 1993-2001 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  10/1993; 4/1998 - 11/2001
- 8037, 1993-2008 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  2/1993 - 1/1996; 3/1996 - 1/1999; 2/1999 - 1/2002; 2/2002 - 1/2005; 2/2005 - 1/2008
- 8039, 1992-2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  7/1992 - 6/1994; 7/1994 - 6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2005
- 8040, 1995-2005 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  12/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 7/2000 - 3/2005
- 8041, 1998-2007 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 7/2004 - 6/2007
- 8042, 1998-2004 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004
- 8043, 1994-2003 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003
- 8044, 1994-2006 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  7/1994 - 6/1997; 7/1999 - 6/2001; 10/2000 - 9/2006
- 8045, 1995-2004 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8046, 1996-2008 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2008
- 8049, 1993-2003 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  7/1993 - 6/1995 (re-Opener); 7/1995 - 6/2000 (MOA); 7/2000 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 12/2002 (MOA); 1/2003 - 6/2003 (MOA)
- 8050, 1997-2008 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  6/1997; 12/1997 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2004; 6/2004 - 6/2008
- 8051, 1997-2010 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  1/1997 - 1/2001; 1/2001 - 1/2005; 1/2005 - 2/2010
- 8052, 1995-2009 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  4/1995 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2009
- 8053 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  5/1995 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2005
- 8054, 1998-2007 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  4/1998; 11/1997 - 11/2002; 11/2002 - 11/2007
- 8055, 1995-2009 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 7/2004 - 6/2009
- 8057, 1995-2005 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  6/1995; 6/2000; 10/2000 - 9/2005
- 8058, 1992-2008 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1998 (MOA); 7/1998 - 10/2001 (MOA); 11/2001 - 4/2005 (MOA); 6/2004 - 4/2008
- 8059, 1999-2007 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  12/1999; 12/2003; 12/2007
- 8060, 1994-2005 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  6/1994 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 9/2005 (XTN)
- 8061, 1993-2008 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  6/1993 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8062, 1994-2005 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  7/1994 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 9/2005 (XTN)
- 8063, 1996-2008 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  6/1996 - 5/1999 (see K 8064); 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8064, 1996-2005 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 7/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8065, 1995-2008 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 8066, 1994-2009 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2009
- 8067, 1991-2008 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  8/1991 - 8/1994; 4/1992 - 3/1995; 4/1995 - 3/1998; 4/1998 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2008
- 8068, 1995-2004 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  7/1995 - 7/1998; 7/1998 - 7/2001; 7/2001 - 7/2004
- 8070, 1996-2003 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  1/1996 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2003
- 8071, 1994-2006 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8072, 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2005
- 8073, 1995-2006 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2006
- 8074, 1996-2009 (Box 52, Folder 15)